Finding Aid for the Andrew West Photographs of the Guelaguetza, 1982-1985
UCLA Library Special Collections
Andrew West Photographs of the Guelaguetza
1982-1985
1713
West, Andrew, 1954-
1 box (0.5 linear ft.) 3 oversize boxes
Andrew West (1954- ) has worked as a photographer's assistant and as an annual report photographer. His photography of Guatemalan costumes appears in the exhibition catalog, Threads of identity, published by the Fowler Museum at UCLA (1992). The collection is composed of photographic materials including color slides, color prints, and a CD-R disk containing color images from La Guelaguetza and Saints Day Celebration festivals held in Oaxaca, Mexico in 1982 and 1985. Also included is documentation about the materials and Andrew West.
University of California, Los Angeles. Library Special Collections. Los Angeles, California 90095-1575
Administrative Information
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Caroline West, 2003.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9948721903606533
Biography
Andrew West is a native Californian, born June 23, 1954 in San Rafael. He attended Chadwick and Palos Verdes High schools on the Palos Verdes peninsula. West's interest in photography began at age 10 when he visited Guatemala with his parents. Early influences on his development as a photographer included family friend and professional photographer Irving Whitman and a return trip to Guatemala. West spent a short time at the University of Utah and took a two year course in photography at Colorado Mountain College. In the late 1970s, he studied visual anthropology under John Collier at the San Francisco Art Institute. West has worked as a photographer's assistant and as an annual report photographer. His photography of Guatemalan costumes appears in the exhibition catalog, Threads of identity, published by the University of California's Fowler Museum in 1992.
Scope and Content
The collection is composed of photographic materials including color slides, color prints, and a CD-R disk containing color images from La Guelaguetza and Saints Day Celebration festivals held in Oaxaca, Mexico in 1982 and 1985. Also included is documentation prepared by Caroline West about the materials and the photographer, Andrew West.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
Color prints.
Color slides.
Documentation.
CD-R disk.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Subjects
West, Andrew, 1954- --Archives.; Guelaguetza Festival, Oaxaca de Juárez, Mexico--Photographs.
Container List
- Color Slides
  - Guelaguetza
    - Slides for print series, 1985., Slides correspond with Guelaguetza print series - (10) 8 × 10”, (10) 11 × 14”, (10) 16 × 20”. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Lunes del Cerro, 1985., 16 slides. (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Lunes del Cerro, balloons lifting banner, 1985
      - Lunes del Cerro, balloons lifting banner, 1985
      - Lunes del Cerro, distance view of band, 1985
      - Lunes del Cerro, distance view of band, 1985
      - Lunes del Cerro, distance view of dancers on stage, 1985
      - Lunes del Cerro, distance view of dancers on stage, 1985
      - Lunes del Cerro, distance view of dancers on stage, 1985
      - Lunes del Cerro, distance view of dancers on stage, 1985
      - Lunes del Cerro, distance view of dancers on stage, 1985
      - Lunes del Cerro, distance view of dancers on stage, 1985
      - Lunes del Cerro, distance view of dancers on stage, 1985
      - Lunes del Cerro, distance view of dancers on stage, 1985
      - Lunes del Cerro, distance view of dancers on stage, 1985
      - Lunes del Cerro, distance view of dancers on stage, 1985
      - Lunes del Cerro, distance view of dancers on stage, 1985
      - Lunes del Cerro, distance view of dancers on stage, 1985
    - Chines de Oaxaca, 1982., 31 slides. (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Chines de Oaxaca, man and stick sculpture [blurred], 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, puppets and women dancing [blurred], 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, puppets and women dancing [blurred], 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, puppets and women dancing [blurred], 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, puppets and women dancing [blurred], 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, puppets and women dancing [blurred], 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, puppets and women dancing, 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, puppets and women dancing, 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, puppets and women dancing, 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, puppets and women dancing, 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, skirts close-up, 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, woman dancer close-up, 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, woman dancing with flower basket on head [blurred], 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, woman dancing with flower basket on head [blurred], 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, woman dancing with flower basket on head [blurred], 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, woman holding flower basket on head, 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, woman holding flower basket on head, 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, woman holding flower basket on head, 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, woman holding flower basket on head, 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, woman holding flower basket on head, 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, women dancing with flower basket on heads [blurred], 1982
      - Chines de Oaxaca, women with long braids (hair), 1982
    - Ejutla de Crespo - Valle de Oaxaca, 1985., 20 slides. (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Ejutla de Crespo, dancers, 1985
      - Ejutla de Crespo, dancing with skirts, 1985
      - Ejutla de Crespo, dancing with skirts, 1985
      - Ejutla de Crespo, dancing with skirts, 1985
      - Ejutla de Crespo, dancing with skirts, 1985
      - Ejutla de Crespo, dancing with skirts, 1985
      - Ejutla de Crespo, dancing with skirts, 1985
      - Ejutla de Crespo, dancing with skirts, 1985
      - Ejutla de Crespo, dancing with skirts, 1985
      - Ejutla de Crespo, dancing with skirts, 1985
      - Ejutla de Crespo, dancing with skirts, 1985
      - Ejutla de Crespo, dancing with skirts, 1985
      - Ejutla de Crespo, dancing with skirts, 1985
      - Ejutla de Crespo, dancing with skirts, 1985
      - Ejutla de Crespo, dancing with skirts, 1985
      - Ejutla de Crespo, dancing with skirts, 1985
      - Ejutla de Crespo, dancing with skirts, 1985
      - Ejutla de Crespo, dancing with skirts, 1985
      - Ejutla de Crespo, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1985
      - Ejutla de Crespo, woman displaying skirt, 1985
    - Ejutla de Crespo - Valle de Oaxaca, 1982., 35 slides. (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Ejutla de Crespo, back view of dancers close-up, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, back view of girl dancer, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, back view of girl dancer, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, back view of woman close-up, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, back view of woman dancer close-up, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, dancers, 1985
      - Ejutla de Crespo, dancing with skirts, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, dancing with skirts, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, earring close-up, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, earring close-up, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, elbow close-up, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, girl dancer close-up, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, girl dancer close-up, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, hand holding skirt close-up, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, hand holding skirt close-up, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, hand holding skirt close-up, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, hands close-up, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, hands close-up, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, hands close-up, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, hands close-up, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, leather sandals close-up, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, leather sandals close-up, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, necklaces close-up, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, performers handing gifts to spectators, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, performers handing gifts to spectators, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, spectators watching dancers on stage, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, spectators watching dancers on stage, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, spectators watching dancers on stage, 1982
      - Ejutla de Crespo, spectators watching dancers on stage, 1982
    - San Antonino Castello de Verasco del Valle, 1985., 20 slides. (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - San Antonino Castillo, stacked vegetables and dancers, 1985
      - San Antonino Castillo, stacked vegetables and dancers, 1985
      - San Antonino Castillo, stacked vegetables and dancers, 1985
      - San Antonino Castillo, stacked food and dancers, 1985
      - San Antonino Castillo, stacked vegetables and dancers, 1985
      - San Antonino Castillo, stacked food and dancers, 1985
      - San Antonino Castillo, stacked vegetables and dancers, 1985
      - San Antonino Castillo, stacked bread and dancers, 1985
      - San Antonino Castillo, stacked bread and dancers, 1985
      - San Antonino Castillo, stacked bread and dancers, 1985
      - San Antonino Castillo, stacked food and dancers, 1985
      - San Antonino Castillo, dancers and turkey, 1985
      - San Antonino Castillo, dancers and turkey, 1985
      - San Antonino Castillo, dancers and turkey, 1985
      - San Antonino Castillo, dancers and turkey, 1985
      - San Antonino Castillo, dancers, 1985
      - San Antonino Castillo, dancers, 1985
      - San Antonino Castillo, dancers, 1985
      - San Antonino Castillo, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1985
      - San Antonino Castillo, spectators watching dancers on stage, 1985
    - Tlacolula del Valle, 1985., 9 slides. (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Tlacolula del Valle, women holding flower baskets on their heads, 1985
      - Tlacolula del Valle, women holding flower baskets on their heads, 1985
      - Tlacolula del Valle, performers and large balloon, 1985
      - Tlacolula del Valle, performers and large balloon, 1985
      - Tlacolula del Valle, performers and large balloon, 1985
      - Tlacolula del Valle, performers and large balloon, 1985
      - Tlacolula del Valle, performers and large balloon, 1985
      - Tlacolula del Valle, performers and large balloon, 1985
    - Tehuantepec - Region de Istmo, 1985., 20 slides. (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Tehuantepec, dancers, 1985
      - Tehuantepec, woman throwing flowers to spectators, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, dancers, 1985
      - Tehuantepec, dancers, 1985
      - Tehuantepec, dancers, 1985
      - Tehuantepec, dancers [blurred], 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, dancers [blurred], 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, dancers, 1985
      - Tehuantepec, dancers, 1985
      - Tehuantepec, couples dancing [blurred], 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, couples dancing [blurred], 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, dancers [blurred], 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, dancers [blurred], 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, dancers, 1985
      - Tehuantepec, dancers, 1985
      - Tehuantepec, dancers, 1985
      - Tehuantepec, dancers, 1985
      - Tehuantepec, dancers, 1985
      - Tehuantepec, dancers standing in row applauding, 1985
      - Tehuantepec, dancers [blurred], 1985
      - Tehuantepec, dancers [blurred], 1985
    - Tehuantepec - Region de Istmo, 1982 & 1985., 33 slides. (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Tehuantepec, dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, women dancers and banner, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, woman dancer close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, woman holding bowl of bread, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, woman holding bowl of bread, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, flowers decorating woman's hair close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, girl handing object to spectators, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, flowers decorating woman's hair close-up, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, dancers and spectators, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, man carrying fake fish on shoulder, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, man carrying fake fish on shoulder, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, man carrying fake fish on shoulder, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, man carrying fake fish on shoulder, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, man carrying fake fish on shoulder, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, man carrying fake fish on shoulder, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, man carrying fake fish on shoulder, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, man carrying fake fish caught by net, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, man carrying fake fish, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, man carrying fake fish chased by nets, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, man carrying fake fish chased by nets, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, man carrying fake fish chased by nets, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, man carrying fake fish chased by nets, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, man carrying fake fish chased by nets, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, man carrying fake fish chased by nets, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, man carrying fake fish, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982 or 1985
      - Tehuantepec, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982 or 1985
    - Juchitan - Istmo, 1982 & 1985., 37 slides. (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Juchitan, dancers and chairs, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, dancers and chairs, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, dancers sitting in chairs, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, dancers sitting in chairs, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, festive decorations, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, flower arrangement, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, performers and festive decorations, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, performers and festive decorations, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, procession, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, procession, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, women and banner, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, women and banner, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, women dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, women dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, women dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, women holding flags, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, women holding gourd bowls and flowers on heads, 1982 or 1985
      - Juchitan, women holding gourd bowls and flowers on heads, 1982 or 1985
    - Pochutla - Region de la Costa, 1982 & 1985., 32 slides. (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Pochutla, children dancing, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, children dancing, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, children dancing, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, couples dancing, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, couples dancing, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, couples dancing, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, couples dancing, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, couples dancing, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, couples dancing, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, couples dancing, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, dancers [blurred], 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, dancers holding hats, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, dancers holding hats, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, dancing with blanket, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, young couples dancing, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, young dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Pochutla, young dancers, 1982 or 1985
    - Tlaxiaco - Mixteca, 1982 & 1985., 40 slides. (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, couples dancing, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, couples dancing, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, couples dancing, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, couples dancing, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, performers throwing straw hats to spectators, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, couples dancing, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, dancing with skirts, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, performers throwing straw hats to spectators, 1982 or 1985
      - Tlaxiaco, performers throwing straw hats to spectators, 1982 or 1985
    - Huautla de Jimenez de la Canada, 1985., 21 slides. (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Huautla de Jimenez, dancers, 1985
      - Huautla de Jimenez, dancers, 1985
      - Huautla de Jimenez, dancers, 1985
      - Huautla de Jimenez, dancers, 1985
      - Huautla de Jimenez, dancers, 1985
      - Huautla de Jimenez, dancers, 1985
      - Huautla de Jimenez, dancers, 1985
      - Huautla de Jimenez, dancers, 1985
      - Huautla de Jimenez, dancers, 1985
      - Huautla de Jimenez, dancers, 1985
      - Huautla de Jimenez, dancers, 1985
      - Huautla de Jimenez, dancers, 1985
      - Huautla de Jimenez, dancers, 1985
      - Huautla de Jimenez, dancers, 1985
      - Huautla de Jimenez, dancers, 1985
      - Huautla de Jimenez, dancers, 1985
      - Huautla de Jimenez, dancers, 1985
      - Huautla de Jimenez, dancers, 1985
      - Huautla de Jimenez, man playing guitar, 1985
      - Huautla de Jimenez, man playing guitar, 1985
      - Huautla de Jimenez, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1985
    - Betaza - Region de la Sierra, 1982 & 1985., 16 slides. (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Betaza, dancers with braided hair, 1982 or 1985
      - Betaza, dancers with braided hair, 1982 or 1985
      - Betaza, dancers with braided hair, 1982 or 1985
      - Betaza, dancers with braids, 1982 or 1985
      - Betaza, dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Betaza, dancers, 1982 or 1985
      - Betaza, men wearing black masks, 1982 or 1985
      - Betaza, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982 or 1985
      - Betaza, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982 or 1985
      - Betaza, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982 or 1985
      - Betaza, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982 or 1985
      - Betaza, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982 or 1985
      - Betaza, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982 or 1985
      - Betaza, women dancers with braided hair, 1982 or 1985
    - Mixistlán (Mixe) de la Sierra, 1985., 19 slides. (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Mixistlán, couples dancing, 1985
      - Mixistlán, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Mixistlán, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Mixistlán, dancers holding leaves, 1985
      - Mixistlán, dancers, 1985
      - Mixistlán, dancers, 1985
      - Mixistlán, man close-up, 1985
      - Mixistlán, performers kneeling, 1985
      - Mixistlán, performers kneeling, 1985
      - Mixistlán, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1985
      - Mixistlán, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1985
      - Mixistlán, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1985
      - Mixistlán, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1985
      - Mixistlán, spectators watching dancers on stage, 1985
      - Mixistlán, spectators watching dancers on stage, 1985
      - Mixistlán, woman close-up, 1985
      - Mixistlán, woman dancer, 1985
      - Mixistlán, women holding leaves, 1985
      - Mixistlán, women holding leaves, 1985
    - Ylalag - Sierra, 1982., 20 slides. (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, couples dancing, 1982
      - Ylalag, performers throwing gifts to spectators, 1982
      - Ylalag, performers sitting with spectators, 1982
      - Ylalag, dancers, 1982